Somewhere in the naked city lurks a one-armed, one-legged, one-eyed man responsible for the murder for
which Ryan Harrison has been wrongfully accused. To find him, all Ryan needs is a clue.
Wrongfully Accused is a action, adventure, comedy film directed by Pat Proft.
Ryan Harrison, a violin god, superstar and sex symbol does not want
to cheat on sexy Lauren Goodhue's husband with her.
Goodhue is found murdered and Ryan suddenly finds
himself being the main suspect.
After being sentenced to death he manages to flee while
being transferred to his execution site.
Now, all the world is after him as he stumbles from one unfortunate incident to the next in order to
prove himself innocent - by finding a mysterious one-eyed, one-armed, one-legged man...
Ryan Harrison, played by Leslie Nielsen.
Fergus Falls, played by Richard Crenna.
Lauren Goodhue, played by Kelly LeBrock.
Cass Lake, played by Melinda McGraw.
Sean Laughrea, played by Aaron Pearl.
Sergeant Tina Bagley, played by Leslie Jones.
Wrongfully Accused is a 1998 parody film written, produced and directed by Pat Proft and starring Leslie Nielsen
as a man who has been framed for murder and desperately attempts to expose the true culprits.
The film is a parody of the 1993 film The Fugitive,
and also parodies numerous other films.
Wrongfully Accused was released by Constantin Film in
Germany on July 23, 1998 and by Warner Bros.
in the United States on August 21, 1998 to negative reviews
from critics while grossing $9.64 million.
The film explores themes of death penalty, falsely
accused, violin, attempt to escape, violinist.
The tone is lighthearted.